{
  "extraDescription": "answers are integers",
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 60,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "8191 &minus; 4892",
      "answer": "3299"
    },
    {
      "question": "2304 &minus; 3415",
      "answer": "-1111"
    },
    {
      "question": "8011 &minus; 9614",
      "answer": "-1603"
    },
    {
      "question": "6392 &minus; 4227",
      "answer": "2165"
    },
    {
      "question": "6997 &minus; 3461",
      "answer": "3536"
    },
    {
      "question": "1840 &minus; 1117",
      "answer": "723"
    },
    {
      "question": "3126 &minus; 5071",
      "answer": "-1945"
    },
    {
      "question": "9495 &minus; 4726",
      "answer": "4769"
    },
    {
      "question": "6435 &minus; 4341",
      "answer": "2094"
    },
    {
      "question": "8921 &minus; 1449",
      "answer": "7472"
    },
    {
      "question": "6202 &minus; 1767",
      "answer": "4435"
    },
    {
      "question": "7457 &minus; 4784",
      "answer": "2673"
    },
    {
      "question": "4095 &minus; 2719",
      "answer": "1376"
    },
    {
      "question": "8709 &minus; 1980",
      "answer": "6729"
    },
    {
      "question": "5568 &minus; 1408",
      "answer": "4160"
    },
    {
      "question": "5098 &minus; 4153",
      "answer": "945"
    },
    {
      "question": "8828 &minus; 4051",
      "answer": "4777"
    },
    {
      "question": "8289 &minus; 7811",
      "answer": "478"
    },
    {
      "question": "1176 &minus; 1064",
      "answer": "112"
    },
    {
      "question": "9635 &minus; 1975",
      "answer": "7660"
    },
    {
      "question": "1774 &minus; 572",
      "answer": "1202"
    },
    {
      "question": "393 &minus; 5841",
      "answer": "-5448"
    },
    {
      "question": "7351 &minus; 1010",
      "answer": "6341"
    },
    {
      "question": "6776 &minus; 5404",
      "answer": "1372"
    },
    {
      "question": "9346 &minus; 411",
      "answer": "8935"
    },
    {
      "question": "8189 &minus; 3527",
      "answer": "4662"
    },
    {
      "question": "8140 &minus; 3107",
      "answer": "5033"
    },
    {
      "question": "4494 &minus; 2646",
      "answer": "1848"
    },
    {
      "question": "9288 &minus; 1551",
      "answer": "7737"
    },
    {
      "question": "8969 &minus; 3924",
      "answer": "5045"
    },
    {
      "question": "6091 &minus; 6004",
      "answer": "87"
    },
    {
      "question": "2164 &minus; 6746",
      "answer": "-4582"
    },
    {
      "question": "3002 &minus; 3321",
      "answer": "-319"
    },
    {
      "question": "9066 &minus; 5051",
      "answer": "4015"
    },
    {
      "question": "5718 &minus; 1555",
      "answer": "4163"
    },
    {
      "question": "8776 &minus; 8324",
      "answer": "452"
    },
    {
      "question": "783 &minus; 721",
      "answer": "62"
    },
    {
      "question": "9431 &minus; 6454",
      "answer": "2977"
    },
    {
      "question": "5076 &minus; 2058",
      "answer": "3018"
    },
    {
      "question": "8014 &minus; 5227",
      "answer": "2787"
    },
    {
      "question": "5061 &minus; 2026",
      "answer": "3035"
    },
    {
      "question": "9045 &minus; 5804",
      "answer": "3241"
    },
    {
      "question": "6814 &minus; 2765",
      "answer": "4049"
    },
    {
      "question": "9120 &minus; 4548",
      "answer": "4572"
    },
    {
      "question": "4258 &minus; 3700",
      "answer": "558"
    },
    {
      "question": "7398 &minus; 443",
      "answer": "6955"
    },
    {
      "question": "4217 &minus; 2945",
      "answer": "1272"
    },
    {
      "question": "4521 &minus; 2475",
      "answer": "2046"
    },
    {
      "question": "8809 &minus; 1259",
      "answer": "7550"
    },
    {
      "question": "8472 &minus; 477",
      "answer": "7995"
    }
  ]
}
